<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Using `pack` on Cloud Native Buildpack Documentation</title>
    <link>/docs/using-pack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Using `pack` on Cloud Native Buildpack Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/using-pack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building app images using `build`</title>
      <link>/docs/using-pack/building-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/using-pack/building-app/</guid>
      <description>pack build enables app developers to create runnable app images from source code using buildpacks.
$ pack build &amp;lt;image-name&amp;gt; Example: Building using the default builder image In the following example, an app image is created from Node.js application source code.
$ cd path/to/node/app $ pack build my-app:my-tag In this case, the default builder (essentially, an image containing buildpacks) is used, and an appropriate buildpack is automatically selected from the builder based on the app source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating app images using `rebase`</title>
      <link>/docs/using-pack/update-app-rebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/using-pack/update-app-rebase/</guid>
      <description>The pack rebase command allows app developers to rapidly update an app image when its stack&amp;rsquo;s run image has changed. By using image layer rebasing, this command avoids the need to fully rebuild the app.
$ pack rebase &amp;lt;image-name&amp;gt; Example: Rebasing an app image Consider an app image my-app:my-tag that was originally built using the default builder. That builder&amp;rsquo;s stack has a run image called pack/run. Running the following will update the base of my-app:my-tag with the latest version of pack/run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with builders using `create-builder`</title>
      <link>/docs/using-pack/working-with-builders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/using-pack/working-with-builders/</guid>
      <description>pack create-builder enables buildpack authors and platform operators to bundle a collection of buildpacks into a single image for distribution and use with a specified stack.
$ pack create-builder &amp;lt;image-name&amp;gt; --builder-config &amp;lt;path-to-builder-toml&amp;gt; Example: Creating a builder from buildpacks In this example, a builder image is created from buildpacks org.example.buildpack-1 and org.example.buildpack-2. A TOML configuration file provides necessary configuration to the command.
[[buildpacks]] id = &amp;#34;org.example.buildpack-1&amp;#34; uri = &amp;#34;relative/path/to/buildpack-1&amp;#34; [[buildpacks]] id = &amp;#34;org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with stacks</title>
      <link>/docs/using-pack/stacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/using-pack/stacks/</guid>
      <description>What is a stack? A stack provides the buildpack lifecycle with build-time and run-time environments in the form of images. If you&amp;rsquo;re using the pack CLI, running pack suggest-stacks will display a list of recommended stacks that can be used when running pack create-builder, along with each stack&amp;rsquo;s associated build and run images.
Using stacks Stacks are used by builders and are configured through a builder&amp;rsquo;s configuration file:
[[buildpacks]] # .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>